Guide to the M. L. Rosenthal Papers ca. 1930-1996 MSS 45 MSS.045
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: M.L. Rosenthal's writing
  - Subseries B: essays, poems, reviews, lectures
    - Lectures / Readings, undated; 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 35)
    - Lectures / Readings, undated; 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 36)
    - Misc. poems, undated; 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 37)
    - Misc. poems, undated; 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 38)
    - Misc. poems, undated; 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 39)
    - Misc. poems, undated; 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 40)
    - Misc. poems, undated; 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 41)
    - Misc. poems (published versions), undated; 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 42)
    - Misc. short papers, abstracts, fragments, etc., undated; 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 43)
    - Notes for reviews, articles, books, talks, undated; 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 44)
    - Reviews (A-G), undated; 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 45)
    - Reviews (H-N), undated; 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 46)
    - Reviews (O-P), undated; 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 47)
    - Reviews (R-Z), undated; 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 48)
    - Reviews (pre-1950), 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 49)
    - Reviews (1950-1959), 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 50)
    - Reviews (1960-1969), 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 51)
    - Reviews (1970-1979), 31142040612171 (Box IV.B.9, Folder 52)
- Series V: Printed Material
  - Subseries A: Rosenthal's publications
    - The 'Actaeon-Principle' in The Southern Review, Summer 1987, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 1)
    - Aerian, pretentios... [Romanian] in Steaua, July 1966, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 2)
    - Alice, Huck,... and "1991-1992 (in memoriam DHR)" in Southern Review, Summer 1993, 1991-1992, 1993; 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 3)
    - Alienation of Sensibility and 'Modernity' in Approaches to the..., May 17-18, 1963, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 4)
    - Alienation of Sensibility and 'Modernity' in The Poetry Review, Winter 1965, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 5)
    - American Elegy in Pequod, no. 35, undated; 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 6)
    - The Aroused Language of Modern... in NYT Magazine, Nov. 24, 1974, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 7)
    - At the Last in Poetry, Oct.-Nov. 1987, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 8)
    - Awake and Remember! in Southern Review, Summer 1992, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 9)
    - Bill Arrowsmith-'Noble Acerbity' in Arion, Spring/Fall 1992-93, 1992-1993; 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 10)
    - A Contemporary Aesthetic Injustice in College English, May 1942, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 11)
    - The Corruption of Aschenbach in U of Kansas City Review, Autumn 1947, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 12)
    - Criticism: Starting from Scratch in The Missouri Review, Spring 1978, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 13)
    - Cultural and Rhetorical Symbols... in Symbols and Values, 13th symposium (1954), 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 14)
    - Discovering E. P. In Paideuma, Fall/Winter 1986, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 15)
    - Early Yeats: Poems Before 1900... in Yeats Eliot Review, Winter 1994, 1900-1994; 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 16)
    - e. e. c. (elan et courage) in Spring, Fall 1994, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 17)
    - Elegy 1991-1992 in Exile, vol. 17, no. 3, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 18)
    - Entretien avec M. L. Rosenthal [French] in La Quinzaine litteraire, 15 Oct. 1971, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 19)
    - Footnote in QRL, vol. 9, no.4, undated; 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 20)
    - Hardy's Satires: Hard Knowledge... in Southern Review, Summer 1991, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 21)
    - Hemingway's Achievement in Pleasures in Learning, Dec. 1961, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 22)
    - His Eye Is On the Critic in Audience, Summer 1959, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 23)
    - His Present Discontents in Shenandoah, Fall 1971, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 24)
    - Horace Gregory's Catullus Translations in Accen t, Spring 1950, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 25)
    - The Humanities-Our Secret Crisis in The Humanist, May/June 1977, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 26)
    - Hurrah for Longinus!... in Southern Review, Winter 1989, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 27)
    - In the World Pub in Exile, vol. 19, no. 3, undated; 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 28)
    - Intermission in AntFus, Autumn 1972, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 29)
    - Like a Man With a Bullet Wound in Review 72, Fall 1972, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 30)
    - Like Morning Light in Salmagundi, Spring 1972, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 31)
    - 'A Midrash of Hieroglyph': Ben Belitt's 'Sumac' in Salmagundi, Summer 1990, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 32)
    - Modern Irish Poetry in Southern Review, Summer 1995, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 33)
    - Modern Poetry in... a scrawny cry, Spring 1964, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 34)
    - 'Modernity' and the New Poetry from The New Poets, 1967, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 35)
    - A Modest Anthology in Review 75, Fall 1975, 31142040612189 (Box V.A.1, Folder 36)
    - Notes on Some Afro-Cuban Translations in Phylon, vol. 6, no.3 (1945), 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 37)
    - Notes Toward an Unauthorized Autobiography in Pequod, no. 23/24, undated; 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 38)
    - Nya Songer Och Ny Song [Swedish] in BLM, Sept. 1963, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 39)
    - October Again, "Wedding.. ." and "A Place in Time" in Southern Review, Summer 1990, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 40)
    - Olson/His Poetry in Massachusetts Review, Winter 1971, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 41)
    - On Being a Jewish Poet in Present Tense, Winter 1976, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 42)
    - On the 'Dissidents' of the Thirties in U of Kansas City Review, Summer 1951, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 43)
    - On Yeats and the Cultural Symbolism... in Yale Review, Summer 1960, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 44)
    - Pinocchio (translated by MLR) in Cricket, Nov. 1993, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 45)
    - Plastic Possibilities in Poetry, Nov. 1971, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 46)
    - poems from Beyond Power in Stations, 1970, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 47)
    - from Poems 1966-1980 [Chinese] in Foreign Poetry, no.4, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 48)
    - Poetic 'Experiment' in Spring, Fall 1995, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 49)
    - Poetic Power-Free the Swan! in Shenandoah, Fall 1972, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 50)
    - Poetry Pilot (guest editor, MLR) April 1987, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 51)
    - Primo Levi (translated my MLR) in Exile, vol. 18, no.2, undated; 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 52)
    - Problems of Robert Creeley in Parnassus, Fall/Winter 1973, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 53)
    - The 'Pure' Poetry of Horace Gregory in Modern Poetry Studies, Spring 1973, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 54)
    - Reality... and "Farewell" in Poetry, Dec. 1967, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 55)
    - review of Dance of the Intellect in Modern Philology, August 1988, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 56)
    - review of Pablo Neruda and Cesar Vallejo in Review '68, 1968; 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 57)
    - Shadow-Runners in Southern Review, Spring 1995, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 58)
    - Snow Man in Ploughshares, Fall 1991, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 59)
    - Steven's Sea Surface Full of Clouds in The Explicator, Mar. 1961, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 60)
    - A Toast to Hugh Kenner in William Carlos Williams Review, Spring/Fall 1993, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 61)
    - Through Streets Where smiling Children in MPS, Autumn 1977, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 62)
    - Two Poems in Northwest, Autumn 1962, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 63)
    - Uncertain Odysseus in Shenendoah, Winter 1968, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 64)
    - Visiting Yeats's Tower and "Geometries of Haifa" in QRL, vol.17, no. 1-2, undated; 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 65)
    - Voyage in Neruda in Review 74, Spring 1974, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 66)
    - The Waste Land as on Open Structure in Mosaic, vol.6, no.1, undated; 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 67)
    - from "The World Pub," Led by the Love.. ." and "Intro." in Ploughshares, Spring 1991, 31142040612197 (Box V.A.2, Folder 68)
  - Subseries B: miscellaneous
    - Misc. journals, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 1)
    - Misc. journals, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 2)
    - Offprints/reprints, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 3)
    - Offprints/reprints, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 4)
    - Offprints/reprints, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 5)
    - Offprints/reprints, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 6)
    - Offprints/reprints, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 7)
    - Offprints/reprints, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 8)
    - Offprints/reprints, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 9)
    - Offprints/reprints, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 10)
    - Offprints/reprints, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 11)
    - Printed material, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 12)
    - Printed material, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 13)
    - Printed material, undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 14)
    - Printed material (see oversize box), undated; 31142040612205 (Box V.B.3, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous printed material (no folders), undated; 31142040612213 (Box V.B.4, Folder data_value_missing_30da60ebb5439233b244e83baacce92e)
- Series VI: Biographical material
  - Biographical, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 1)
  - Biographical, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 2)
  - Biographical, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 3)
  - Biographical, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 4)
  - Biographical/Juvenilia (see oversize box), undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 4b.)
  - China, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 5)
  - Confessions, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 6)
  - Juvenilia, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 7)
  - Juvenilia, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 8)
  - Juvenilia, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 9)
  - Juvenilia, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 10)
  - Juvenilia-correspondence, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 11)
  - Memorial for MLR, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 12)
  - MLR's bibliography (original handwritten and typed sectioned), undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 14)
  - Writings about MLR, undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 15)
  - Writing about MLR: reactions to NYT piece, etc., undated; 31142040612221 (Box VI.A.1, Folder 16)
  - American Literary Scholarship, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 17)
  - Bibliographical material, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 18)
  - Book-related (early stages), undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 19)
  - Book-related (early stages), undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 20)
  - Book-related (notes), undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 21)
  - Book-related (notes), undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 22)
  - Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs-Division for Americans Abroad, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 23)
  - China, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 24)
  - College thesis, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 25)
  - Conference of science, philosophy and religion, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 26)
  - Contracts, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 27)
  - Course-related, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 28)
  - Course-related, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 29)
  - Courses and notes, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 30)
  - Courses and notes, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 31)
  - Coursework notes, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 32)
  - Delmore Schwartz Award, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 33)
  - Delmore Schwartz Award, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 34)
  - English 282: Background of English Restoration Theatre, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 35)
  - English G41.3926: Readings in Modern Poetry, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 36)
  - English G41.3927: Modern Irish Poetry, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 37)
  - English G41.3954: Poetic Criticism, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 38)
  - English V41.0600, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 39)
  - Exams, undated; 31142040612239 (Box VI.A.2, Folder 40)
  - The Humanist, undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 41)
  - Journals, undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 42)
  - Mss, undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 43)
  - Mss, undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 44)
  - Mss, undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 45)
  - Mss, undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 46)
  - Mss, undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 47)
  - Misc., undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 48)
  - Misc., undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 49)
  - Misc., undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 50)
  - Misc., undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 51)
  - Misc., undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 52)
  - Misc., undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 53)
  - Misc. notes, undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 54)
  - Misc. notes, undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 55)
  - MSU: Eng 7028400-Literary Concepts, undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 56)
  - NEH Summer Institute, undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 57)
  - NEH Summer Institute, undated; 31142040612247 (Box VI.A.3, Folder 58)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 59)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 60)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 61)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 62)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 63)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 64)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 65)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 66)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 67)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 68)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 69)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 70)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 71)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 72)
  - Notebooks, undated; 31142040612254 (Box VI.A.4, Folder 73)
  - Notes-Eliot, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 74)
  - Notes on criticism, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 75)
  - NYU-related, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 76)
  - Orals, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 77)
  - Playbills, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 78)
  - Playbills, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 79)
  - Playbills, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 80)
  - Poetics Institute, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 81)
  - Present Tense (including correspondence and mss), undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 82)
  - Present Tense (including correspondence and mss), undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 83)
  - Programs, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 84)
  - Programs, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 85)
  - Programs, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 86)
  - Programs, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 87)
  - Programs, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 88)
  - Programs, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 89)
  - Programs, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 90)
  - Publishers, undated; 31142040612262 (Box VI.A.5, Folder 91)
  - School notebooks, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 92)
  - Student notes, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 93)
  - Student notes, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 94)
  - Student notes (incl. poetry), undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 95)
  - Student papers, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 96)
  - Student papers, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 97)
  - Student papers, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 98)
  - Student papers, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 99)
  - Syllabi, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 100)
  - Tax and legal papers, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 101)
  - Tearsheets with MLR poems, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 102)
  - Trips, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 103)
  - Undergrad comps: bibliography, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 104)
  - Undergrad comps: grammar, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 105)
  - Undergrad comps: linguistics, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 106)
  - Undergraduate exams, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 107)
  - University of Pennsylvania, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 108)
  - Yeats seminar, undated; 31142040612270 (Box VI.A.6, Folder 109)
  - Address books and calendars (no folders), undated (Box VI.A.7, Folder data_value_missing_14a3a4436063f901ba706f1d4b0e23b4)
  - (Accretions 2000) misc. notes and letters pulled from Rosenthal's books while cataloguing them at Fales, undated; 31142040612288 (Box VI.A.8, Folder data_value_missing_5ebe321ce05026bbd814d68477a8887f)
  - (Accretions 2000) materials from Rosenthal's office at the English Department, undated; 31142040612288 (Box VI.A.8, Folder data_value_missing_bc718f9850336c144c8448cb552df51d)
- Series VII: Production files
  - Blue Boy on Skates, undated; 31142040612296 (Box VII.1, Folder 1)
  - The Genius of Modern Poetry, undated; 31142040612296 (Box VII.1, Folder 2)
  - The Genius of Modern Poetry, undated; 31142040612296 (Box VII.1, Folder 3)
  - The Genius of Modern Poetry, undated; 31142040612296 (Box VII.1, Folder 4)
  - The Genius of Modern Poetry, undated; 31142040612296 (Box VII.1, Folder 5)
  - The Genius of Modern Poetry, undated; 31142040612296 (Box VII.1, Folder 6)
  - The Genius of Modern Poetry, undated; 31142040612296 (Box VII.1, Folder 7)
  - The Genius of Modern Poetry, undated; 31142040612296 (Box VII.1, Folder 8)
  - New Modern Poetry, undated; 31142040612296 (Box VII.1, Folder 9)
  - New Modern Poetry, undated; 31142040612296 (Box VII.1, Folder 10)
  - Pinocchio, undated; 31142040612296 (Box VII.1, Folder 11)
  - Pinocchio, undated; 31142040612296 (Box VII.1, Folder 12)
  - Pinocchio, undated; 31142040612296 (Box VII.1, Folder 13)
  - Pinocchio, undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 14)
  - Pinocchio, undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 15)
  - Pinocchio, undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 16)
  - Poetry and the Common Life, undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 17)
  - The Poet's Art (proofs), undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 18)
  - The Poet's Art, undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 19)
  - The Poet's Art, undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 20)
  - The Poet's Art, undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 21)
  - The Poet's Art, undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 22)
  - Sailing Into the Unknown, undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 23)
  - Sailing Into the Unknown, undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 24)
  - Selected Poems... by W. B. Yeats, undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 25)
  - Selected Poems... by W. B. Yeats, undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 26)
  - She, undated; 31142040612304 (Box VII.2, Folder 27)
- Series VIII: Photographs
  - Photographs of MLR, family, and others (in archivally-sound photograph sleeves), undated (Box VIII.1, Folder data_value_missing_29f568324a5d05d15ef841804969f23f)
- Series IX: Audiovisual
  - Audio cassette tapes, two reel-to-reel tapes, and one microfilm (no folders), undated (Box IX.1, Folder data_value_missing_529fd1589b460e1d97d748fd997d3db3)
  - Reel-to-reels, undated (Box IX.2, Folder data_value_missing_1a7c140801a93d0880b59676417fa2f2)
- Oversize
  - Series 5B, folder 15-misc. printed material, undated (Box Oversize 1, Folder 1)
  - Series 6, folder 4b-biographical/Juvenilia, undated (Box Oversize 1, Folder 2)